<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Alican Toprak</title><link>https://alican.de/page/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Alican Toprak</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 22:48:08 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alican.de/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Archives</title><link>https://alican.de/archives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alican.de/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://alican.de/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alican.de/about/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://alican.de/about/coding.jpg" alt="Featured image of post About" />&lt;p>Hi there, I&amp;rsquo;m Alican Toprak, a driven and passionate software developer based in Frankfurt, Germany. I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinated by technology and the limitless possibilities it offers, which is why I pursued a career in software engineering.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As a Senior Software Engineer at Adesso SE, I have the opportunity to bring my expertise and passion to the table every day. But my interests extend far beyond just software development. I also have a love for cooking, coffee brewing, woodworking, and bicycling. These hobbies allow me to tap into my creative side and explore new avenues of self-expression.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve created this personal web page to share my journey with others. From my latest software projects to my latest coffee brewing experiments, I want to inspire others to pursue their own passions and interests. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re interested in technology or just love a good cup of coffee, I hope my site will offer something for everyone.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So come along for the ride and let&amp;rsquo;s explore what&amp;rsquo;s possible together! I can&amp;rsquo;t wait to connect and share my findings with you.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Categories</title><link>https://alican.de/categories/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alican.de/categories/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://alican.de/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://alican.de/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>